const questions = [
    {
        // Question 1
        question: "With respect to bylaws and rules in a strata development, which of the following statements is TRUE?",
        choices: ["Bylaws are passed by ¾ vote of the strata council.",
        "Bylaws provide for the control and management of the strata lots and common property.",
        "When a bylaw or rule violation relates to the use of a recreational facility that is common property or a common asset, the strata council may require the sale of the owner’s interest in the condominium complex.",
        "All of the above"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        // Question 2
        question: "Gretel and Hansel have decided to jointly purchase a strata lot as their new residence. They choose a brand new strata lot located in Dessert Village, which includes such amenities as a gym, tennis courts and saunas. To finance their purchase, Gretel and Hansel grant a mortgage to Grimm, who also has mortgages for 75% of the other strata lots in Dessert Village. Recently, the residents of Dessert Village have been in disagreement with respect to the use of the tennis courts. The strata corporation has called a meeting to determine whether there should be an appointment system for the use of the sports facilities. Gretel thinks that people should have to make a reservation to use the tennis courts; Hansel thinks it should be first come, first served. Which of the following is TRUE?",
        choices: ["Both Gretel and Hansel have lost their right to vote by granting the mortgage to Grimm; only Grimm will have the right to vote.",
        "There is only one vote per strata lot; therefore, either Gretel or Hansel may cast a single vote on this matter. Regardless of any provision in the mortgage agreement, Grimm has no right to vote on this issue because it does not affect the security for the mortgage.",
        "Gretel, Hansel and Grimm have one vote between them. If they cannot all agree on how to vote, then the chairperson will discount their vote on this matter.",
        "Grimm has no right to vote because he has not provided at least five days’ written notice to the strata corporation that he will be exercising his voting power. The result is that both Gretel and Hansel will have one vote each."],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        // Question 3
        question: "Naomi is thinking of purchasing a condominium. She has obtained a copy of the rules and reviewed the bylaws registered at the land title office. She has more questions about the strata corporation, so she asks Tina, the trading services representative, how she can get this information. Tina suggests that Naomi request an Information Certificate in Form B from the strata corporation. Which of the following questions would NOT be answered by the Information Certificate?",
        choices: ["What is the amount of the strata corporation’s contingency reserve fund?",
        "Are there any legal proceedings pending against the strata corporation?",
        "Are there any judgments registered against the strata lot Naomi is thinking of purchasing?",
        "Are the expenses of the strata corporation for the current fiscal year expected to exceed the expenses budgeted?"],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        // Question 4
        question: "Charles was in the habit of playing his stereo too loudly at night after 10:00 p.m. He has received notice that the strata corporation has a bylaw providing that no strata lot owner may allow an unreasonable noise level in their strata lot after 10:00 p.m. When Charles seeks his lawyer’s advice, she correctly states that:",
        choices: ["the bylaw is not valid because it was not passed by the strata council.",
        "the bylaw is not valid because bylaws passed by the strata corporation may only regulate the operation of the common property.",
        "the bylaw is void because it infringes on an owner’s use of their strata lot.",
        "the bylaw is valid."],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        // Question 5
        question: "Henry lives in an entirely residential strata complex and owns a large dog. Under a section of the bylaws, he has been given notice by the strata corporation to remove his dog. Henry has kept the dog in his strata lot since he purchased the lot three years ago. It has never caused any complaint, until now. Henry is the only owner who has an animal. Which of the following courses of action is available to Henry?",
        choices: ["If he could obtain support of 75% of the owners, he could have the bylaw amended.",
        "He could apply to the Civil Resolution Tribunal for an order prohibiting the corporation from exercising its affairs in this way, as it is significantly unfair to him.",
        "He could have an arbitrator appointed.",
        "All of the above courses of action are available to Henry."],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        // Question 6
        question: "Bill owns a strata lot. His unit is 2,200 square feet. The other seven units have a combined area of 17,350 square feet. The common property has an area of 4,200 square feet. The annual common expenses are $45,000. What is Bill’s monthly share of the common expenses?",
        choices: ["$421.99",
        "$5,063.94",
        "$475.50",
        "$347.36"],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        // Question 7
        question: "Strata Corporation VRX123 has adopted the Standard Bylaws set out in the <em>Strata Property Act</em>. Assume the annual total contribution to the operating fund is $50,000.00. In the annual budget, an expenditure of $2,000 for window cleaning has been authorized. Which of the following statements is TRUE?",
        choices: ["The strata council may pay the $2,000 window cleaning fee without any further consent.",
        "Because the fee is higher than $500, the strata council will need to call a meeting of the strata corporation and obtain approval by ¾ vote.",
        "Under the Standard Bylaws, a strata council may pay any amount up to $2,500 without permission from the corporation, whether or not it is contained in the budget.",
        "If this is a common property expense, the strata council has complete authority to any amount."],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        // Question 8
        question: "Which one of the following actions does NOT require a ¾ vote by the strata corporation?",
        choices: ["An amendment to the bylaws",
        "Adoption of a resolution to pay strata council members for their services",
        "Adoption of a new rule governing common property",
        "A designation of limited common property by the owners"],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        // Question 9
        question: "The Owners, Strata Plan, 1234 (the “Strata Corporation”) is a strata corporation based out of Courtenay, British Columbia. The Strata Corporation is getting ready for its FIRST annual general meeting (“AGM”). One key topic up for discussion is the Strata Corporation’s contribution to its contingency reserve fund (the “CRF”). Which of the following is TRUE regarding the Strata Corporation’s required contributions to its CRF at the time of the first AGM?",
        choices: ["The Strata Corporation is not required to contribute to the CRF at the first AGM, given that the developer already paid a lump sum to the CRF.",
        "The Strata Corporation must bring the CRF to at least 50% of the total amount budgeted for the annual operating fund.",
        "The Strata Corporation is not required to contribute to the CRF at the first AGM, given that the Strata Property Act does not mandate the Strata Corporation to contribute to the CRF until the fifth AGM.",
        "The Strata Corporation must contribute a minimum of 10% of the total amount budgeted for the annual operating fund to the CRF."],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        // Question 10
        question: "Which of the following statements about strata property management service agreements is FALSE?",
        choices: ["A strata property management contract will generally end on its expiry date.",
        "When a strata management contract ends the strata manager must retain all strata corporation records for four weeks after which the strata manager is permitted to destroy the records.",
        "If the strata property management contract does not provide for early cancellation before the expiry date, section 39 of the Strata Property Act permits a strata corporation to cancel the contract before its expiry upon two months’ notice to the brokerage if the cancellation is first approved by a ¾ vote at a general meeting.",
        "A brokerage can cancel the contract before its expiry by giving the strata corporation two months’ notice."],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        // Question 11
        question: "Which of the following spaces are considered a “habitable area” in the context of unit entitlement calculations?",
        choices: ["Balconies",
        "Closets",
        "Garages",
        "Patios"],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        // Question 12
        question: "A number of strata lot owners in Pacific Palace, a strata complex, are unhappy with the current allocation of strata fees. They wish to change the way strata fees are allocated at Pacific Palace. Which of the following statements about the allocation of strata fees is TRUE?",
        choices: ["Pursuant to the <em>Strata Property Act</em>, the allocation of strata fees must be allocated based on unit entitlement and cannot be changed.",
        "Strata fees may be allocated in a manner other than unit entitlement by passing a resolution with a ¾ vote approving a new formula and registering the resolution and formula.",
        "Strata fees may be allocated in a manner other than unit entitlement by passing a resolution where only the members of the strata council must unanimously vote in favour of the change.",
        "Strata fees may be allocated in a manner other than unit entitlement if a resolution approving the new formula is passed by a unanimous vote, and this resolution is filed in the land title office."],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        // Question 13
        question: "Which of the following statements about common property is TRUE?",
        choices: ["The owners, as tenants in common, own the common property, each in the proportion set out in the Schedule of Unit Entitlement.",
        "The owners, as tenants in common, own the common property, each in the proportion set out in the Standard Bylaws.",
        "The owners, as joint tenants, own the common property, each in the proportion set out in the Schedule of Unit Entitlement.",
        "The owners, as joint tenants, own the common property, each in the proportion set out in the <em>Strata Property Act</em>."],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        // Question 14
        question: "Caroline is the registered owner of a strata lot in The Sentinel, a luxury strata property in West Vancouver, British Columbia. When she purchased her lot, she was told that it included a parking stall. Caroline has come to learn that the parking stall is designated as limited common property (“LCP”) for the exclusive use of her strata lot. Which of the following statements about Caroline’s rights regarding the parking stall is TRUE?",
        choices: ["The stall’s LCP designation will automatically expire when Caroline sells or transfers title to her strata lot.",
        "The LCP designation gives Caroline the right to preclude access to the parking stall to anybody for any reason.",
        "While Caroline has the right to use the LCP, she must allow the strata corporation reasonable access to the LCP.",
        "As the parking stall has been designated as LCP, there is no way for the owners to revoke this designation in the future."],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        // Question 15
        question: "Jeremy is a prospective purchaser who is seeking to purchase a strata lot located in a strata property called Pacific Palace which is owned by Sarah. Jeremy requests a Certificate of Payment from the Pacific Palace strata corporation. In response, the strata corporation must:",
        choices: ["",
        "comply with the request within 10 days, so long as Sarah has agreed to pay disputed funds, which the strata corporation alleges she owes, into court.",
        "include claims against the owner that are pending in court, an arbitration panel, or the Civil Resolution Tribunal on the Certificate of Payment.",
        "not charge Jeremy a fee of more than the amount that is prescribed in the Strata Property Regulation in order to process the request for the Certificate of Payment."],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        // Question 16
        question: "Which of the following statements about annual general meetings is TRUE?",
        choices: ["The developer must hold the first annual general meeting within six weeks of the passage of nine months from the date of the first conveyance of a strata lot to a purchaser unless there is a conveyance of 50% plus one of the strata lots before that time.",
        "The owners must elect a strata council for the first time at the second annual general meeting, and until that time, the developer serves as the first strata council.",
        "Under no circumstances is the developer obligated to hold the first annual general meeting before six weeks after the passage of nine months from the date of the first conveyance of a strata lot to a purchaser.",
        "If the developer fails to hold the first annual general meeting as required, the developer must pay to the strata corporation $1,000 for every 30 days of delay."],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        // Question 17
        question: "Monterey Manor is a condominium building in Coquitlam, British Columbia containing 80 strata lots. The roof of the building is at the end of its life and needs to be replaced. The strata corporation is seeking to raise the funds necessary to replace the roof by applying a special levy against the strata lot owners. Timothy, the strata manager at Monterey Manor, properly advises the strata corporation that:",
        choices: ["a strata corporation may only apply a special levy if there is not enough money to cover the expense in the contingency reserve fund.",
        "if the strata corporation intends to collect contributions to the special levy according to the Schedule of Unit Entitlement, a ¾ resolution is required.",
        "if the strata corporation intends to collect contributions on a basis other than the Schedule of Unit Entitlement, a ¾ resolution is required.",
        "a strata corporation may struggle to collect special levies promptly, as charging interest on late special levy payments is strictly prohibited."],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        // Question 18
        question: "Gerald is a strata manager who has been asked whether each of the following expenditures can be paid for using funds from the contingency reserve fund (the “CRF”). Gerald correctly identifies that the strata corporation can spend funds from the CRF in order to:",
        choices: ["pay the landscaping company that trims the hedges on the property each month as specified in the service contract.",
        "repair a wall in the parking garage, which an engineer has advised will become a safety hazard if not repaired within two years, without requiring approval from the owners.",
        "replace a section of the roof covering common property, if the repair is approved by a ⅔ vote at a general meeting, assuming the repair is not recommended in the depreciation report.",
        "modernize the elevator system, if this expenditure is recommended in the depreciation report and approved by a majority vote at a general meeting."],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        // Question 19
        question: "Through its bylaws, a strata corporation may legally:",
        choices: ["impose a rental restriction which requires Nolan, an owner, to evict an existing tenant in order to comply with the bylaw.",
        "impose a rental restriction which prohibits Felicity, an owner, from renting her lot to Jazmin, her sister.",
        "impose an age restriction of 55+, which prevents Tom, who is 30 years old, from becoming a tenant",
        "restrict all owners from having any and all animals on strata premises."],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        // Question 20
        question: "Which of the following statements comparing cooperative ownership and strata title ownership is TRUE?",
        choices: ["Cooperative ownership bestows an individual fee simple title to the cooperative owner’s unit, while strata ownership bestows shares in the strata corporation.",
        "The strata corporation holds title to the land on which the strata property exists, while a cooperative corporation does not.",
        "Strata properties and cooperatives can both exist on either land held in fee simple or leasehold land.",
        "A strata lot owner must obtain approval of the strata council in order to sell their interest, while cooperative ownership is freely alienable."],
        correct: 2
    }
            /*
        {
            // Question x
            question: "",
            choices: ["",
            "",
            "",
            ""],
            correct: 0
        },

        */
    /*,*/
    // add more questions here...
];